hey ready ready oh you're gonna why do
you love me yeah Oh everyday why do you
love me I think well I loved you
probably before you actually loved me I
think the way that I love you now I
think I definitely loved you before you
laugh but I think I loved or love how
passionate you are like that's like the
first thing that I was like so attracted
to so I just love your passion just for
life and for your relationship with God
and all those things and because God
told me to I don't use your choice think
about this well I mean that's like the
main reasons because you're a good man
so I asked for my pals yes that looks
like you were writing I know that's so
weird
who are these yeah yeah a little less
legible
how about legit looks exactly like your
writing that's very bad not bad look
it's never a fault
like we read it what I'm not I grew up
in a generation we not to write anything
I wish they taught us calligraphy is a
perfect okay so when was the moment you
knew you loved me well this is
interesting
because I think if I were now looking
back because I can say it would be now a
lot more but I think I knew I loved you
when we started hanging out like my
first friends but I just had a cannon so
much like other shit and overlapping
things in my life look like total
insecurities and things were obvious I'm
not ignoring it and then eventually
sabotage it so I knew I mean if I was
just like not at that I'm just gonna be
like you're my buddy this is a great no
problem you know and then the moment we
started like dating and getting close I
was just like trying to like put it in
like a little compartment because I was
like I knew it was like
you know yes I was not I was not like
bullshitting myself I was like oh okay
yeah so it was like you know you know
are you directing this map that's okay
describe your first impression of me
well let's see my first impression of
you you're obviously dating Lauren okay
well you were dating my best friend and
we were really young and I just
remembered you were really really like
funny and just full of energy and so
naturally everyone's attracted to that
type of personality so that was my first
impression just kind of like he's so fun
and he's like so cool I always thought
you were like so cool I was like he's
like so cool yet cool friends
so like I read what I was like 15 that
was technically for a suggestion
and then there was like another first
impression later wouldn't there be well
but that's my first impression that's
cool
what what's your three favorite memories
that we've shared mm-hmm
should we wait for that plane since
there's like an airport right here hmm
that's actually hard to choose in a good
way
the first one that comes to my mind I
might like go out of order
chronologically it's like our first like
turnaround trip to California when you
got hired at done here and that was your
first job there buddy to LA and a high
audition for the voice and made it
season three and then we came right back
Oh week week or so later but that was
like Taniya I was like that was a really
strong memory I'm just like cuz it was
like the start of like so much other
stuff you know especially now I'm living
here over couple years let's see I think
that when we first started dating I
remember when a very strong memory it
was just like those it was like wine bar
that we first like and I was connected
no one to sorry
oh no no La Paloma it was more that La
Paloma was at the Starbucks
yeah we like I know unfortunately I was
better coffee but know when we first I
thought like hey let's have a business
meeting
and you shared all this really dope shit
about like your vision for I was like
that I think that's when I was first
oh my god this is crazy like because you
shared all this come credible like
vision about like your beauty stuff and
and I was like really like now I was
like now you're like going because like
really pumped because it's like about
entrepreneurship stuff like all of your
huge vision for like now you like
surpassed all that stuff already anyways
for the most not really other than like
the cool coloring book ideas really
perfect yeah but like all that stuff I
remember that was really strong I think
an obvious like oh we can go this fast
Tuesday when I proposed to you and you
said yes to becoming my wife that's
pretty good that's my favorite you got
me you shocked me
I was that good one my turn that's right
no no no it's yours actually is it yeah
this is fun
when do you feel closest to me I think
that's a good question I think I feel
closest when and this could be an
interesting thing but like the first
thing that came to mind was when we
might be disagreeing on something but
you kind of I'm able to communicate with
you in a way that you understand and
then you not necessarily compromise but
you're just really sensitive and like
understanding about it and I feel just
like I'll thank God you know what I mean
so I feel like really close when you're
just like understanding whether or not
maybe you agree or something like that
but you're just kind of like okay honey
like data and I'm maybe that can be
reciprocal but I feel like really close
to you at that point something yes it's
a win all right
right why does it feel like a win well
just that's cool that's good to know I'm
like oh yeah take that I got it and we
got a camera in case I forget it like
said
just because I feel like I mean
obviously in any relationship the
hardest thing is communication between a
male and a female and just understanding
each other and what kind of things are
extremely upsetting to me that maybe
aren't upsetting to you but for you to
just step back and go okay this doesn't
really make sense to me but like I'm
going to I guess yeah maybe the word is
compromised and just understand that
it's not about like you know I don't
have to understand and the fact that you
just kind of let it I don't know I don't
explain it but you know I mean like when
we just kind of come to some sort of
resolve yeah I'm still wearing that well
we both are yeah but I think that that's
when and we're getting better and better
I thought which is great and I think
that that's and I feel closest cuz I'm
like we can do this yeah okay
what do you think is the hardest thing
for me right now
that's big what do you think the hardest
thing for me what do you think is the
hardest thing for me right now mm-hmm
I guess it's like let's see I think that
well I guess there's a few different
things that's like a let's see what do
you think that means to you though no no
I think practically
you know like obviously right now where
things are at like there's so much great
stuff that we've been building and
obviously like and I knew it was the
right thing like to get engaged
obviously we both feel like a strong
sense of peace for that but I think
what's probably hard is fully like
trusting the process because not
everything's like in order you know
right now I'm learning to trust more and
more than me probably he's really hard
and more and more and you know God and
he's leading us to which can seem really
really psychotic at times and really
unreliable and like completely the exact
opposite of like what most stable people
would do and insane people would do yeah
I bet you that's hard being with an
insane person but like you know I can
imagine no I wear that sometimes I'm
sure I do I wear that sometimes I'm
thinking like wow that's got to be so
hard for her because I don't know me and
obviously I you know me but you know I
always worry about that like being
difficult to be like me I can probably
have the worst I can have like this and
that that and I think even in your your
own self to you
entrepreneurial goals and your own
career goals and life goals and things
like that so the gap between like it
feeling like it's really really close
and not a time especially like right
right now specifically the director of
the cards that's that makes sense um
started
what are you hesitant to tell me I think
like at this point I mean I think these
conversations kind of come up a little
bit but I get hesitant to imagine your
career as a musician blowing up just
because it's scary it's like there's
like
like all the things like because I know
the music is so good I love it but it's
just hard because I see like how just
these men just become like completely
like like sex and bulls in like they're
just like so the attention is all on
them and so I obviously just struggle
with so much insecurity as it is so -
like even think about all these eyes
like on you and just like mm-hmm that
lifestyle is just so tough so like for
us because we've like struggled past
with just like so much shit then it's
just scary to me and I know that like
our relationship is solid and like
obviously being engaged is helpful but
it still doesn't a gate the fact that
like I just get so worried that like I
don't know you know like I don't know
like that's it's just like so hard cuz I
want to be so supportive and I am but at
the same time it's like I get hesitate
cuz I'm like well yeah but what about my
career like I want my stuff to blow up
and like you have this whole energy like
around your team and and just like a lot
of our stuff parallels so much so then
it's like and we've kind of talked about
this but like just I just don't want to
be left in the dust of like your music
blowing up and then you just being like
oh yeah well I make youtube videos and I
know that financially if that does
happen for you cuz then I could just
like kind of do whatever I want and
produce shit like this which is what I
want but that's just like yeah scary
like all of it scary to me just other
girls and like all that shit like the
music industry is just so gross so
that's like thankfully like we're
Christians and like all that I know will
be different
it's just hard okay thank you
it turns out you won like it's just
gonna be shitty if like like you've
already seen how I get with like other
girls so like it's gonna be hell I feel
bad for that like if I see any I'm like
uh-uh don't even like freaking flip out
that's what I said I said no there's no
girls and I'm like that's not happening
what could I do to improve our
relationship
it's nice what could you what could I do
so what can you do what can I do what
can you do I think just in general like
I said to you before and it's obviously
like you know with not a sturdy past
that's pretty late to leaner and I
understand that but just like what I
know and like where I'm at like even
like in my heart and when I see for both
like I think what could really improve
our relationship and just you in general
would just be like I think just really
taking a chance to trust me more Milan
things and you know you have a you're a
strong woman you know and you have a lot
of tendencies to like do things on your
own and I think you're learning more to
like find the value in that and I just
think like the world would open up you
know in our relationship I think if
there was a deeper level of trust like
we continue to like explore you know
what I mean
and I want that I want that like full
confidence we just like you don't have
to like kick and scream sometimes and
like
because I'm like getting back of my head
I'm just like shaking my head to say
like seeking to understand you know
because that's a half of that I'm like
you understood and you could show me
that you can understand where I'm coming
from me you would see that I'm swimming
you know you can see that how i'm having
your best interest their heart more than
i think i get credit for but it's
changing that's the what i'm saying i'm
even recently i'm seeing like total
shifts who knew that that finger was
like the magic ring you know just in
general like allowing that space to like
right yes oh I guess the bottom of the
barrel is good I said am I the best sex
you've ever had
oh cool seriously no but my hey
background no no not like that but I
just mean like the answer is clearly you
remove me from the darks - I saw the
light
it's so embarrassing like that should be
like no you like you like helped out the
King where do you want to expand that no
okay well there you have it
when do you get jealous of me being with
others um I'm not as you know I'm not
like the jealous type
in general when I I'm really not maybe I
should be more sometimes no because um I
think there's times if I do get jealous
it's a number like time because I like
spending time with you and where I get
most jealous if it's like you know
something or someone or even if it's
like something you know stressful or
whatever that's like taking you away
from the lake sometimes anything makes
you feel like you can it's not
necessarily people I'm like I would
never worry about late if he went on
camera yeah that question probably
would've been better if it was for me
my and maybe yeah I don't really I guess
it's a good thing you know but I'm just
not like that anyways I might just get
jealous when I get sent on work trips to
Disney World in your case yeah that is
fair enough I'm just like that's dumb I
should go yeah for four days in Disney
World for work I definitely could be a
part of that I got yeah
do you know just ask one no I'm good at
this what's the biggest sacrifice you've
made that I haven't acknowledged that's
a good question the biggest sacrifice
that I've made that you haven't
acknowledged yeah what's the biggest
sacrifice you've made
I mean cuz I feel like I've definitely
made lots of sacrifices and that was
vice versa but I think that you do a
really good job of acknowledging it but
I'm trying to think of one that like I
feel like you have anything or maybe not
I know
I mean maybe I mean like this is like
kind of silly but like the thing that
comes to mind I mean like I think again
we'd like to discuss this but maybe like
a big sacrifice has been just having you
and Gracie you know sharing my space
which is your dog so having you and now
we have two dogs and two humans in my
room and obviously really sharing that
space right now and so I think that
that's I mean but you pretty much
acknowledge it for sure like we've
talked about this but I think because
like what I'd create is a lot of the
times from my room and so I think that's
just like so stressful to try and feel
inspired to like film in that space when
there's just not which I'm so glad we're
moving but I think that's like probably
one of the biggest sacrifices in the
last its I'd say like few months for
like year whatever but yeah this was on
the I wrote gonna see my penmanship yeah
it's a lot different than than
penmanship on these curtains I see
I mean something I don't know what is it
okay whatever just a secret that you
have been afraid to tell you yeah but
let's get juicier I know you're not
gonna tell me what I want to know like
so why don't you just ask me the
question I don't know like that's what
I'm saying it's obviously there's stuff
that I don't know so what is something
that you're like she doesn't need to
know that yeah I feel like I don't
really have any like secrets like we've
kind of already been there and covered
that stuff it's like I don't really like
keeping secrets if you were like ask me
like a point-blank question I could be
like okay okay then what's something
specifically in the last couple years
that you've never told me that you know
I would be upset about or you've been
like not telling me just because you're
trying to protect me being sad or that's
that's such a loaded question I'm like
getting myself like in trouble yeah I
mean like the only thing that comes to
my mind was like just all that the time
where I was like my taking time with
like the ex situation and I'm just like
brushing a lot of I just wanna dismiss
this from my life
yeah so I was like for me I was like
trying to think about that and at the
same time like knowing that really
knowing her like we had much more like
at stake was like put me in an
interesting position because it's like
all right like you know if it was like
okay
damned if I do damned if I don't you
know if I'm being authentic even if I
know that I know this is probably going
to like self cracked one way or another
and being authentic about that but also
being out and about like I knew in my
heart like it was gonna work itself out
like between you and I but it was just
like a really weird time so I like
obviously I'm smoothing over things
about your things like you know like
communication or hearing from her or
whatever okay yeah okay here you go
here's mine
there's my actually that's not Bannon
ready I think a nice pace yeah uh-oh
what is the question I said well this is
a my curiosity because obviously like
it's always been curious not you know
I've been supportive himself of like
you've dated girls for like a long time
for me and there's still certain things
that come up where I'm kind of curious
like okay what does that mean I don't
wait too that you know at all so my
curiosity this is a specific question
but over the past three years that we've
been dating on and off three plus years
that we've been dating on and off while
we were off did you date or what if you
know that once well maybe I mean I was
making once that was like maybe I don't
have divulge no I don't think so
I don't know wait a minute wait a minute
I like to remember no wait no but really
it was like nothing to be worried about
when was this a long time ago I was when
I was living in moral a drive house I
think I don't like have to think about
it just Megan you didn't kiss any other
girl but that's your next girlfriend
yeah but I was like not even oh come on
what's weird because it was like you're
not yeah but you are off really right so
you're entitled to a girlfriend because
it's a girl and so it's fine
no that's not how it works what happened
oh you did Wow like how long ago what's
a long time that could be like three
weeks or something out the longer no
like literally it was when we weren't
even living out here yet and you and I
were just starting to talk so he said
since we've been off and on
that's like the Marley Drive that
doesn't make sense
I don't remember I don't remember I
honestly I just remember I there's that
there's that weird nervous laugh no
really I'm like trying to piece it
together I I thought no I'm really I'm
not lying I swear to God I think it was
during the time when I came out here to
visit because I remember going it was
I'm getting confused because we also
hung out once
the Marley Drive house but it was not
even like that so I think it was
actually before I moved out here and I
was visiting for my birthday actually
it's weird you have such a detailed
specific memory I just say yeah no I
mean I would
I'm answering I think you don't know is
your verdict is because there was not a
big deal
oh that's how ass yeah I'm answering the
question so did you go on a date with a
girl yeah no they all asked still okay
know if anyone it was not female so you
would have to be worried about what you
knew that that's not anything like
honestly that's not what you should have
been worried about when we were not
together it was the other guys that I
was dating that's what I'm worried about
huh that's not what I was worried about
I know I don't know why okay that's was
curious me I would be a lot more concern
about guys which now is not a problem
but like I don't know why you put too
much focus on that kind of stuff cuz it
doesn't matter well it matters in
certain in certain moments I like still
like it still lingers a little bit as
far as like attracting the girls but
there's no action but it's still curious
I'm still curious about it because it's
still present in some way or another I'm
not like worried about it like as far as
if the relationship but it definitely
don't have like this like fluid
attraction and males are involved
females are involved and you're involved
you would be like what the fuck
what so I was out we I'm you're not
gonna get a what the fuck out of me
you're gonna get fill me fill in the
blanks
no question like you know empathize if
you either and I'm like I come left with
like all right you know and so in some
situations because I'm kind of like okay
I think I understand but then there's
like little curve balls that come where
I'm just like Kaylee fill in the blanks
you know Mike help me understand more
because I obviously can't relate to that
in a parallel way you know so it's like
that's why I wrote that question not
about me because I'm actually glad it's
about that cuz that's an easy answer
then questions about when you and I were
off and I was doing other people so I'm
glad that's one thing like that's not
even anything to be worrying about
okay so what should I worry nothing
that's a different question that you
didn't get and we were stuck no you
should be worried now I'm saying in the
past yeah there was a lot to be worried
would you share you just avoid you just
evaded my entire question and just
rerouted it to something that was it's
irrelevant to me in this question like I
asked you that for a reason you know
okay what is the question well yeah okay
so the answer's no have you been dating
on our did you go on a date and worry
physical with if you don't know we
technical answer's no that's saying like
even just recently there's been
conversations about like you and you're
attracting females and that's something
that's a concern to me like what you do
with what you choose to tell me about
the people you've dated other people you
told me about other people didn't talk
to you I mean you think it's relevant
I'm like to me that's something that's
curious
I'm genuinely curious about because I'm
like I don't understand it right well
that's a different question
okay okay that's not the question you're
asking the question the answer to that
is no okay but if you're asking a
different question of like should I be
concerned when we're married if you're
going to watch you know me with a girl
or something that's how it is
well then what's the question yeah I
mean if ever a spinoff of that question
will just be like explain that it's more
open than anything I'm not like saying
yes or no cuz yes or no it's easy it can
be like technically speaking no
technically speaking yes but the nuance
that's important it's a
like the details you know the tell us
the details and most things so it's like
if I'm seeking to understand you and
that's a part of you that seems very
like suppressed at times but they it
pops up in what's wrong but I'm okay
like whatever
you know I still curious about it it's
still a part of you you can't like fully
oh do we need a timeout
and
yeah do we just continue over that song
okay anyway yeah it's just thank you for
me it's like that but to me and like
what's interesting more than like our
concern just like things that I don't
know about they just get like it's a
part of you obviously yeah I don't think
I brush them to the rug at all like I
think I'm pretty open with you like I've
said in the past I think you think about
it a lot more than you think then you
speak a lot like you might be processing
it and I think there's certain times
even when I hear you sharing I'm like I
think in your mind you're like think you
talk about a lot more because you would
just say little it's like a bit like
little sparse things and I kind of have
to like puzzle piece in there there cuz
it's like one little thing in your head
you have all the details but it's like a
little like tiny little thing that you
say and that's the only thing I hear but
your mind like how do you not know like
I totally said that cuz you say these
little things out of context but it's
like I don't know what's underneath that
you know so you just get little pieces
of things and I have to try to jumble
them together and make my best
assessment of what that means purse is
like right okay so that's a lot of
rambling but what is the actual question
cuz I guess I don't really understand
what's going on because I'm like if you
if you want to ask us it's okay like I
said where did that how does that
resolve like there's obviously you still
like a uncertainty in you - I'm just
like wondering what that means to you
I mean I was having this conversation
with Nick Palacios just recently like I
think that's why our dynamic is so
unique just because I feel like I found
the perfect partner because you
understand we even talked about this I
feel like last night just like how in my
experience and I feel like several other
people's experiences like sexuality can
be very fluid and it doesn't have to be
like oh you know I'm gay I'm lesbian I'm
bisexual
none of that I'm like no there have just
been certain instances where I'm like
attracted to that person and it's caused
me not only just like a lot of really
fucked up hurt and stuff like that cuz
it's just very confusing I knew
immediately when I met you I was like oh
I choose this person and I didn't know I
mean for a while I was like maybe I will
end up with a woman I was open to that a
long time ago but now after meeting you
it was like I definitely know like you
had me at hello I knew that that wasn't
an issue anymore so it's not a matter of
oh well that's dead now it's just like
no I choose you and I would never do
anything to like fuck that up at this
point you know I mean like in the past
there I mean there was so much like it
was so like this with us that that very
much could have been you know a
dangerous place to be but I just am so
grateful that God has moved us so long
and we're not there anymore
you know just because that's like a very
dark place to be
- trust me what do you get okay what do
you get from your faith that supports
our relationship what do you get from my
face that's what we share at the core
okay
what would make you leave me well I mean
at this point it have to be something
really major but since we're not married
yet
and that would be even tougher but I
mean at this point I think it would have
to be finding out if like you were lying
about stuff I guess
yeah I think yeah like if I found out
the like you know you're lying about
stuff like with Maddie or whatever or I
I don't know right you know which it
would have not stuff from the past
necessarily but it would have to be like
if there was stuff like because I asked
you that just recently you know you're
really not an issue and I trust that so
but that or I mean going back to kind of
like what I just get so emotional about
is just like if you take off and like
you're this like whatever and you've got
this whole career in music and then you
just kind of get lost in it which I
don't see you doing at all but you just
never know you know so like I mean I
again I know you and I know right I mean
I think it's just hard for anybody but
like yeah it has to be something like
wild like that
okay who has more power in our
relationship that's a weird question
I don't know I think just like with like
stronger with strong personalities or
something we both have them but gigantic
biceps that's why we're this jacket yeah
yeah but not like you know not like a
domineering way that's good no not like
I'm like this no no I think I think just
in general like maybe yeah long as
you're cool it's annoying if I would
have said me you're a girl those girls
those women they're like you're strong
independent woman I wear the pants in
the relationship I'm like no please
that's a very bizarre for us it looks
better I think yeah you would
self-destruct if I wasn't like Carol I
like yielding to like it's like less
stressful to like if you want to that's
so weird I'm just traditional Maui and I
watched my mom well I think I'm more
comfortable making decisions and things
at times that's where I knew you're
better at making decisions
the world yeah okay okay
what is one experience you wish we never
had see that's I mean this is I feel
like this is such a universal question
cuz like everyone would say well oh but
this is like how we got here today which
is true I would agree cuz I think it's
like what's the one thing I wish you
didn't do but it's kind of interesting
questions like what's one experience you
wish we never had it's kind of
interesting I mean I think yeah I'm like
I don't know I mean I wish that we
didn't have to experience like you'd
like kind of your whole process of like
trying to like I don't know like I just
we now have to work through so much
because of like the past of you not
really being I knew I knew that you
loved me and I knew that it wasn't that
you were unsure of me but I think you
were maybe unsure of yourself and like
certain things so I think that that just
like cause such it's like taking ten
steps back because we had to go there
like we both knew that we loved each
other where you both knew that we would
get to this point but all the shit that
went came with it was just like dating
other people and like it's just like
silly but it's like again it's like
that's kind of an interesting question
cuz it's like like
like I wish we could have just taken
somewhat of a shortcut in some of it
because it's like it was so stupid and
it was just like it caused so much pain
that like didn't wasn't necessary yeah
and now that causes a breach in trust
you know yeah when like if you were to
just listened from the beginning it was
just like I cut off on like little
trails all over the place then but and
then was annoying ironic thing is though
even is that I'm glad you figured it out
with Maddie for a little bit because
then I would have still won wondering
now yeah so I'm like I am so freakin
glad that that happened because I was
like okay in the background laughing
like I'm so stupid like I know that's
not gonna work but go ahead try just
figure that out like if that's gonna
work
I mean it's painful but I'm just glad
that that happened now because I could
not be engaged now not knowing there's
no way yeah not a chance
yeah I knew that's it oh no I don't all
right
well okay what do you wish you could
heal in me and what pain would you take
away
hmm I think I wish I oughta sleep ain't
about disappointment or you know
distrust and even I think some of the
stuff you touched on I'm even from my
kids I like things that maybe like
even the stuff that you shared when you
were in a transition explained you got
heat from both sides against you so to
me that's crazy what's your biggest
regret I mean I don't think this even
relates to us at all I think I think
when I look back at my time of just
speaking of that whole thing of just my
time of self exploration and figuring
out who I was and all of those things I
think that I just don't I was just like
yeah like I'd every pride and just like
so open about it
that I look back now older as an adult
or as a more mature adult now because I
wasn't it open to technically um and I
just regret now seeing what other
parents have to go through with their
kids like all they want is the best for
their children so I think for my parents
it was just a huge slap in the face
because instead of doing my best to
communicate
kind of what I was going through I think
I just was like honestly if you aren't
with this than by and just like shut
them out for four years which obviously
is now not the case but still I just
feel like that's like you know I don't
really you know I'm not the type but
like that's one thing that I look back
now and I go oh that was someone mature
just yeah like I should have been a
little bit more sensitive to that and I
see other people doing it now and that's
been a unique experience for me to be
like hey but like think about your
parents like I know that they're not
trying to like be mean they just want
the best for you and that is scary for
your daughter too now and just be kind
of confused to suit to she is sexually
so I think yeah just not every gret not
I think I did try and communicate I
don't know it's just like such a
interesting thing but I think at least
being a little bit more respectful yeah
instead of just putting all over okay
are we good
what do you think is the biggest
challenge of our relationship you really
do I know that's kind of a similar
question that we have um do you think
the biggest yeah I think that was very
similar I guess I could reiterate it
though I think the biggest challenge of
our relationship is that both of us and
this is different answer to I think both
of us have such a strong faith and have
such a strong commitment to like that
but also I think we both have similar
points of empathy for people have
nothing to do with that which is like
we're kind of bridges I think in certain
ways where we've kind of fallen into I
would never like label myself that but
it just seems like where we are like you
know working so heavily in the music
industry now and you working in like
you know the industry as well in
different facets and like it just seems
like we have like two very sometimes can
be very polar opposites worlds you know
what I mean they seem like it almost
like nemesis or something like that but
we're kind of uniquely displaced like in
both it just kind of happened that way
and I think we we both have an
understanding of these very different
paradigms and I think that will be a
that's a really beautiful thing because
I'll always err on the side of like and
you total you on the like humanity and
just people like you know just being
humans and all the good stuff but you
know a challenge could be like there are
very very bold very clear statements in
our faith that sometimes like to buy
those people that we may be like shake
hands with you know and like have
different yeah it works with so I think
that could be a challenge in our
relationship as we go on is there might
be like different opinions about who we
are and what we're about Oh from both
sides and I think that's just like that
is what it is it's just people that will
probably be a challenge now in probably
forever is what it is yeah a good thing
I don't think either of us struggle with
having opinions okay here we go last but
not least for you Oh
read yours what are the next steps in
our relationship
well next big step in our relationship
that's definitely a big step and the
little steps leading up into that would
just be like thinking in a more peaceful
place like living lies and you know
planning all that stuff out but that's a
big step and then I think our careers to
you know really being catalyst for each
other anything at what that looks like
and where we're gonna like melt together
and help each other you know in
different areas I think that's those
career careers and obviously marriage
whatever order that comes in seems like
they're kind of in parallel babies a lot
a lot of kids you're gonna change your
mind when you see when you see like the
first child you're gonna be like I'm not
doing this service of the world if I
don't make more of these little suckers
you know like just - yeah - good more
food just say some people are families I
want a militia
I want a little army okay you can have
like our own soccer team got nice to her
own school that's not the point
what oh here's one okay what are maybe
two or three things what some advice if
I were to be a better man for you and
better you know partner what are like
two or three things like bits of advice
you can give me to be better for you
I think I mean truthfully jeez I feel so
fucking blessed because like probably
like I hit the jackpot because I think
that you are just I feel badly for other
people honestly almost in every
relationship cuz I'm like most men are
not like you so I feel like you already
your mind is like way up here and like
most men are just like like oh my god so
annoying they know because I found out
much later we weren't dating whoever you
dated anyway but I think so I just want
to like obviously highlight that because
I think that I'm I think I think we've
talked about this to like you know you
are in the right relationship when you
need to feel lucky to have each other
but I definitely am like no I'm the
lucky one for sure just because you're
so like understanding and stuff and just
emotionally intelligent like that's a
real thing and I think that a lot of
people don't know what that is and they
don't exercise that and run towards it
and that's something I mean obviously
and even this type of setting I always
know that you're gonna be by my side and
like we always challenge you know
expanding our minds and that means like
really cool but I think I mean just
again like working on you know which we
are already but just being sensitive and
like different things that like you may
I don't need you to understand
necessarily but just if I'm
communicating like hey that that really
upsets me or whatever just being like oh
really sensitive to the point where you
feel nauseated just because you're like
oh my gosh this is so stupid I hate
having to be like like baby her but
there's certain things I'm like I don't
care if you don't get why it that's me
but it does so just like from the for
okay I'm so sorry like instead of just
being like it's not a big deal
I'm like no it is
and vice-versa I can take that on myself
but yeah I don't think they maybe be
more sensitive I think just continuing
like I've said this before but always
just like being the leader spiritually
because I think I need that I think
you're a lot more spiritually I don't
know how exactly for that I just know
that what I see for my partner like the
ideal partner for me is someone that's
just constantly challenging me in my
walk with God and just like initiate
like I agree with you and you've said
this in the past like that has to be
something that like you want to do on
your own which I do and I feel so
grateful that God has like gotten ahold
of my heart and I do seek that but as my
partner and a leader of my home and my
future family like I just always want
you to be the one that's like hey you
know its prey or like hey like they're
just little things like that and like
let's start our morning devotional like
all those things that like I definitely
want for us I think if you were the one
leaving that I would get like excited
about that okay that's great I think it
could be something to not do as well
yeah okay well here's one so I think
just like you know I think I'm just
being sensitive to the fact that like I
mean and I I relate to this too but I
guess it's different because it's coming
from a different dynamic but you're just
a very friendly guy and I think we've
talked about this in the past my dad's
very friendly he was in the
entertainment business as well but never
letting anyone confuse that for you
flirting because I don't want any eyes
on any side whether it's that female
thinking that you're flirting because
we're being too friendly or whether it's
other people in the room
thinking that that's the case just
because that's like so frustrating so I
think just oh and I think you are really
good about that definitely but just
again in the future like oh just like
around so many different thing and we
both are so I'm taking this unlike
reciprocating and we're both mirrors but
I think just like making sure that could
never be taken wrong ever you know what
I mean mm-hmm
even like respectful in the fact like no
number like nothing like just even like
what kinda what we talked about the
other day
just like talk to linen about it cuz
that's the more respectful thing to do
it's hard because we're like young and
in LA and like networking and all those
things but like I just think it's tough
because that can be taken so wrong like
oh yeah like let me text it like I just
it's a tough thing but I think that
that's